[
  {
    "question": "In 2009, a man in Florida was arrested for riding a lawnmower while drunk. He told police he was on his way to ___.",
    "solution": "a bar"
  },
  {
    "question": "William Shatner raised $25,000 for Habitat for Humanity by selling his ___.",
    "solution": "kidney stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Japan, there is a museum dedicated entirely to ___.",
    "solution": "rocks that look like faces"
  },
  {
    "question": "A town in New Mexico named ___ is the only town in the US where you can mail a letter with their special postmark during the holiday season.",
    "solution": "Santa Claus"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2012, a Norwegian boy escaped from wolves by playing a ___ on his phone.",
    "solution": "heavy metal song"
  },
  {
    "question": "The hashtag symbol (#) is technically called a ___.",
    "solution": "octothorpe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before becoming a famous actor, Danny DeVito worked as a ___ in his sister's salon.",
    "solution": "hairdresser"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Switzerland, it is illegal to own just one ___ because they get lonely.",
    "solution": "guinea pig"
  },
  {
    "question": "NASA once accidentally erased the original recordings of the ___ and had to use TV broadcast copies.",
    "solution": "moon landing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The longest hiccuping spree lasted 68 years and was suffered by a man named ___.",
    "solution": "Charles Osborne"
  },
  {
    "question": "The inventor of the Pringles can, Fredric Baur, requested that when he died, his ashes be buried in a ___.",
    "solution": "Pringles can"
  },
  {
    "question": "Oxford University is older than the ___.",
    "solution": "Aztec Empire"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1932, Australia lost a war against ___.",
    "solution": "emus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cleopatra lived closer in time to the ___ than to the construction of the Great Pyramid.",
    "solution": "Moon landing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The shortest war in history lasted only 38 minutes and was between Britain and ___.",
    "solution": "Zanzibar"
  },
  {
    "question": "A group of flamingos is called a ___.",
    "solution": "flamboyance"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2008, a dog in China was trained to walk on its ___ legs after losing its front legs.",
    "solution": "hind"
  },
  {
    "question": "The original name for the search engine Google was ___.",
    "solution": "Backrub"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before alarm clocks were invented, people in England hired ___ to wake them up in the morning.",
    "solution": "knocker-uppers"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2016, someone paid $10,000 at an auction for a ___ shaped like a chicken nugget that resembled a famous figure.",
    "solution": "chicken nugget shaped like George Washington"
  },
  {
    "question": "Honey never ___. Archaeologists have found 3000-year-old honey in Egyptian tombs that was still perfectly good.",
    "solution": "spoils"
  },
  {
    "question": "The national animal of Scotland is the ___.",
    "solution": "unicorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are more possible iterations of a game of chess than there are ___ in the observable universe.",
    "solution": "atoms"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2015, a man legally changed his name to ___ to protest against the UK government.",
    "solution": "None of the Above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nintendo originally started as a company that made ___.",
    "solution": "playing cards"
  },
  {
    "question": "The inventor of the fire hydrant is unknown because the patent was destroyed in a ___.",
    "solution": "fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "In medieval England, animals could be put on ___ and were actually given lawyers.",
    "solution": "trial"
  },
  {
    "question": "The longest English word without a vowel is ___.",
    "solution": "rhythms"
  },
  {
    "question": "Astronaut Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was ___.",
    "solution": "Moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "A ___ is the only animal that can't jump.",
    "solution": "elephant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Samsung's first product was ___.",
    "solution": "dried noodles"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2006, a woman sued ___ for $1.7 million because their product didn't match the advertisement.",
    "solution": "Nutella"
  },
  {
    "question": "The dot over the letters 'i' and 'j' is called a ___.",
    "solution": "tittle"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first item ever sold on eBay was a ___.",
    "solution": "broken laser pointer"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1994, a prisoner in West Virginia tried to escape by covering himself in ___.",
    "solution": "toilet paper"
  },
  {
    "question": "Coca-Cola was originally ___ colored, not brown.",
    "solution": "green"
  },
  {
    "question": "The fear of long words is ironically called ___.",
    "solution": "hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia"
  },
  {
    "question": "The youngest pope in history was approximately ___ years old when he took office.",
    "solution": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2014, a man in India set a world record by eating ___ ghost peppers in two minutes.",
    "solution": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Great Wall of China was held together with a mortar made of ___.",
    "solution": "sticky rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "A jiffy is an actual unit of time equal to ___.",
    "solution": "one hundredth of a second"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first person convicted of speeding was going ___ mph.",
    "solution": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "In ancient Rome, ___ was used as mouthwash.",
    "solution": "urine"
  },
  {
    "question": "The average person walks the equivalent of ___ times around the world in their lifetime.",
    "solution": "five"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2013, a pizza was delivered to the ___, making it the most expensive pizza delivery ever.",
    "solution": "International Space Station"
  },
  {
    "question": "The world's oldest known joke is about ___.",
    "solution": "a fart"
  },
  {
    "question": "IKEA's Billy bookcase is so popular that one is sold every ___.",
    "solution": "5 seconds"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bananas are technically classified as ___.",
    "solution": "berries"
  },
  {
    "question": "The inventor of the AK-47 later said he wished he had invented ___ instead.",
    "solution": "a lawnmower"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2009, the country of ___ temporarily disappeared from Google Maps due to a glitch.",
    "solution": "Nicaragua"
  }
]
